{
    "id": "420168e826024851b4b213592ca193b2",
    "title": "General Grammar Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "……………….. Rahul, it is a nice film.",
            "description": "According to Rahul means ‘if what Rahul says is true.’",
            "answers": [
                "After",
                "According to",
                "As for"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c543d77868684c26ae6febf8e5977854"
        },
        {
            "question": "Let’s swim ……………… the river.",
            "description": "We use across to talk about movement in water.",
            "answers": [
                "along",
                "over",
                "across"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "6ccad7a081504d5b939055b03309bc63"
        },
        {
            "question": "She is ………………. to refuse.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "polite person",
                "too polite person",
                "too polite a person"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "ae37be1638b34834a655b02efd40262b"
        },
        {
            "question": "She arrived ………………. after breakfast.",
            "description": "Right can mean just or exactly. Rightly means correctly.",
            "answers": [
                "right",
                "rightly",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "d45d29794e0f401aa88cac801b56287c"
        },
        {
            "question": "Peter isn’t here. John isn’t here ………………..",
            "description": "After mentioning a negative idea or fact we can add another negative point by using ‘not…either’.",
            "answers": [
                "also",
                "either",
                "neither"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "8434947038fc40bb8856163a69a1a504"
        },
        {
            "question": "It is important that he ………………. told.",
            "description": "Both structures are possible. In American English the structure without ‘should’ is preferred.",
            "answers": [
                "be",
                "should be",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "cb3cbfb2903540cf8f93a492fb38dbce"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………….. having worked hard, she failed the exam.",
            "description": "Before a noun or an ing form we use in spite of. Although and even though are conjunctions used to connect clauses.",
            "answers": [
                "Although",
                "Even though",
                "In spite of"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "6b8002024b3045909f63c55fbc75d4d6"
        },
        {
            "question": "I’m anxious …………….. my brother.",
            "description": "Certain adjectives which describe people’s reactions and feelings are often followed by a to-infinitive. Anxious is one of them.",
            "answers": [
                "contact",
                "to contact",
                "to contacting"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f2295431ee0b4a5383442031bc78e218"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ……………… somebody coming.",
            "description": "To say that we hear something at the moment of speaking we use ‘can hear’. ",
            "answers": [
                "can hear",
                "am hearing",
                "was hearing"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "5edb6e0ee0634c98907bd130419ff540"
        },
        {
            "question": "I had hardly closed my eyes …………….. the telephone rang.",
            "description": "Both when and before are possible here.",
            "answers": [
                "when",
                "than",
                "before",
                "All of the above"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "73bf80b2ce9b4f5a8e850d4225c633c1"
        },
        {
            "question": "I had no sooner closed the door .....................… somebody knocked.",
            "description": "Sooner is a comparative form. We use ‘than’ after it.",
            "answers": [
                "than",
                "when",
                "before"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "71a6b36dfe8e406dbd7b6627c9d24448"
        },
        {
            "question": "No sooner ……………….. to marry him than she started to have terrible doubts.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "did she agree",
                "had she agreed",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "16416ceccabc4f17be436626ee6dfd9b"
        }
    ]
}